VISHAL MOKASHI

Front-End Developer

Banglore, India

\(+917676208117

☑ vnmokashi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vishalmokashi-a58b2523a

Github - 🞧

https://github.com/VishalNM7676

Design Portfolio - Bē

http://be.net/vishalmokashi

Expertise

HTML

CSS

BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT

REACT

REACT-REDUX

FIGMA

Soft Skills

- · Open-mindedness
- Critical thinking
- Communication
- Good listening
- Teamwork/Collaboration
- Learnability

Summary

Front end developer with skills in writing efficient and scalable code along with a vision of growth with company and utilise my in-depth knowledge of UI/UX development and responsive designing to create exceptional interfaces and user experiences and working efectively with clients and creative teams.

Tools



Work Experience

Chukki Takkies - UI/UX Designer (March 2021 - November 2021)

Freelance as UI/UX Designer & Developer.
Designing and developing responsive webapp, pages & Mobile Apps.
(Janauary 2022 - June 2022)

Internship

(React-JS) Achivers IT

Course Duration: July 2022 - December 2022
Have ability to design and develop efficient user interfaces for web applications while continuing to leran and also expand my knowledge of

emerging web technologies.

Project

Name: AIT E-Commerce Website

Description: Designed UI using CSS3 and Bootstrap5. It has Add to cart feature developed using Javascript with local storage, here you can Increase/decrease Quality. Remove products from cart. And also, it has strict Form Validation. Login features and user can update the pasword.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP5, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS & REACT-REDUX

Hard Skills

• HTML-5

HTML

CSS-3

Ħ

Bootstrap

Javascript

ReactJS

• React-Redux 🐡 + 岛

• Git



· High fedility design

Wireframes



· User resarch & persona Prototyping 뮈

• Graphic design 👗



My Projects

- Age Calculator (JS)
- Form Validation (JS)
- Calculator (ReactJS)
- Password generator app (ReactJS)
- · Shopping-cart app (ReactJS)

Hobbies

- Playing cricket
- Travelling

Languages

- · English,
- · Kannada,
- · Hindi,
- · Marathi.

FRONT-END WEB DESIGNER RESPONSIBILITIES

To Deliver responsive, cross-browser compatible and accessibility complaint websites, achieving 19% faster load time than industry average

Expanded features, refine code, and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement.

Utilizing Redux library to handle state management efficiently which maintain consistency across client, server and native environments.

Extracurricular Activities

Presented paper in the One day national seminar on "MISSION CHANDRAYAAN" held on 14th September 2019.

Presented paper "GREEN ECONOMY" in one day National Conference held on 14th February 2020.

Education

Certificate course in UI/UX Design

Bsc - Rani Channamma university belgavi

2017 - 2020

63%

HSC - Karnataka state PU board

2015 - 2017

62.8%

SSC - Karnataka state board 84.8%

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above information provided by me is true to the best of my knowledge. Yours faithfully

(Vishal Mokashi)